okay so like many classes this is a
really helping just we just read into it
you know are really in our philosophical
thinking incorrectly that's Jeff Lewis
was going you would want to play it out
of this future life switches yourself is
it the endless cognition ascetic of the
room was today and so part of the idea
of stopping the desire for teachers to
do Stella visualizing pollution and
primarily we chose a subway density
global appreciation we're tired and will
focus your attention must get out of the
de chinon this is money we do starting
with the pathetic and absolutely
skittish a mister know that life is
suffering he aspects and with the cosmic
origins of our real day and so I read
the reading you know I didn't know I was
gonna do this until today so is also
fast trashed
yeah but there's too much dolls
I think all the ocean the reading is
really lovely interesting isn't Rosetta
no sugar we need some of the verses and
then we'll talk about - yes - I missed
it because it took my steps for the rest
of the course of this class is to stop
the desire for a small little certain
ages align you and usually so think over
and over how deeds and their fruits
never fail and the cycles of suffering
never fail joke we must stop for future
lives stir than uniquely than your
provider with cylinders very complex
right to the future we we normally think
I hope my future births q1 and really
get into a realm that's gonna be
pleasurable and we established a
miserable - yeah you know that is
around well you know that there are some
existences right presently that course
doesn't the Ovilus district so on yeah
yeah that's going to sell out that of
course we're in the desire realm correct
one left which is just there's this one
of the lines around and it within the
desire realm I mean that's different
aspects support of that include lower
than human and higher than human just
boarded it and you know who's reaching
we're not animals
we're not hungry ghosts we're not in
lower hell roams when you're not doing
demigod neurons which are but
interesting in our context of lush other
texts to be born in one of those films
the line is those it just feel is it
just we're gonna in a sense be
removed from ourselves to change to move
its or someone we really wouldn't want
to be boring when is rhizosphere
we actually have meditations that's a
couture
designed to be born in one of those two
walls a lot of meditations are designed
to go to when you close for this rounds
which are those two extremely ambitious
and for me this life years millions of
years we kind of related sometimes to
Jesus but we know in our in our teaching
so we know in the in the teachings of
the wheel of life that starts to change
these realms will just fit end into a
lower Reaper it's guaranteed because so
really cause the you know around the
status in the register Hamas does every
see is probably the the launchpad and
the best image to get enlightened in one
a lifetime ålesund it'll look more than
that future rabbis about what's in the
sickle for more than pleasure or more
promise but but that's not the case yeah
this idea of I'm tired use yo see when
you Monica could understand life yeah
tossed over oh it's not over so in the
process of karma we must learn the
correlations of government functions
Richard goody let's see when it karma of
Buddhist did a great job instead of us
requesting present does especially
[Applause]
so the laws of karma who can tell me if
there's like one little cotton one don't
anymore because it get away
yeah you can say like it makes Mike yeah
yeah bad you plant a seed partner
motivation but stereo but in the similar
result that's it's it's a component it's
the ocean that will create or see market
or the solution and it's simple order
here the neotec pros there are very
subtle parts of key element to us you
know what is your intention and what are
the components of the intention
you know we keep it PCI we say situation
artichokes you know the function of
karma I said earlier today to a lot of
you that were using karmic seeds look
for your future you much six years from
now twelve years to do you nervous to
the punch yourself that are in Swedish
or in this room right now that's
stealing a conscious on though it's just
us and what we want to avoid so that I
just look at yes so it goes because
you're one effort Jim I don't know sit
back which I wasn't understand that your
system in this room
not killed so further quite nationís you
mean that pretty really Westar would
never the proceeds are so sky nice
expression adjustable pounder
the Dharma initially in his room the
daughter was somehow or another you you
know all of us should do this about the
Buffalo pits thank you very much
Josephine or Joe for my task or exceeds
school for Kenya steel does that seem a
disturbance directly and so we must have
planted it comes awful disease stuff
you'll remember that episode use a couch
or at least makes it up for me hmmm
where I don't know I don't know I don't
I don't know my pastor don't spend much
time we're thinking about them we live
in a town where there's more past life
regression therapists so like makes like
that is such a quintessential ago Rica
like every character let's not
complicate option is Laura and then a
four-step program program which a first
step idea guide you into the proof of
that I think you better stick because I
really say when we're on tour for all
good we think it's less than two legends
doesn't mean the doors remain stupid
Garrett and you loose with them that I
was but there's some other seed in there
were Sarah
I led them with some boosted so it may
be word ecclesia understood you can't
believe or just make we're all standing
there to answer questions in the same
division of ro16
today yeah Bravo I found my partner
children I actually turned my business
around yes with business all of the
above it is a mystery and in that moment
you brother Joe a year before
if Spurs just what beautiful boys dance
function in a way that's the reward it
takes you over to them at the lovely
mother got a good way proud of it does
that what a life-changing moment for you
you're gonna testify dinner later so get
the mood introverted menorahs these laws
is a coronation to all of the countries
haven't seen a series justice or service
all your bullsh forces yesterday charged
to the Sheila losing track of time
today there see what you should have to
do to lessen the resocialize or who
remove the arthrosis to control who
should improve words and I cry mistress
in jail so yes like makes like but on
average that photo good results come
from good deeds bad results hello Cheryl
does the prosciutto
farmer plants corn and pineapples come
up don't
next slide
increases if maybe expand that's
explosive the idea we taught this course
I don't know when you did the numbers it
was 31 trillion that are seeds right
it's just a second subsequent blow
so the introspective your be a suspect
or a census but also the Mosport
episode
it's possible since they are long live
as long as pretty immediate access to
see meeting by much like same as Croesus
is that you so all of you would do it
was enough if she's friends on the
factory memorable remarkable karmic
possibilities of their life should those
regional economies was more if I plan to
see a Norwegian by giving history
episode you'll see me know maybe Judy
issue Michaels giving tons of hundred
dollar bills away guess Michael they'll
see that was still very good Europe to
monitor Dylan
I mean word is a recipient or do you
know a third of my annual income and
then the treatment affordable choose
dessert ellipses I mean because you know
why why is he doing which one was what's
what's visual okay personal bleach now
you know motivation to us well he's
showing us number one in in a DCI tour
he's guarantee showing into six weeks
he'll get a tux
I'm good idea first only simplified I
don't know I don't think well you know
basically what he's doing is really
don't deal with my song we talk about
endowments for our nonprofits thank you
ten years could we raise five or ten
million dollars
you know to perform again our Diamond
Mountain secured make ACIP miss GI
having some kind of a wonderful is abuzz
no she staged don't worry about spending
our precious time raising much to me
that's one of his motive and so when
he's on tour he'll give because
thousands of dollars away not well
exponential if you know what's the
Shimon I experienced an iVillage the
sky's the limit here let's just deal
what what do you want
Trudy for church well I don't know I I
want I want to stick around and see what
happens for the next 25 years
yeah a job we should what's better it
was dismissed Oprah's injured this is
the most exciting thing on the planet to
me some nervousness as my probable death
doesn't mean I don't get to move engines
musica to recognize the Bullock girl -
no you did Section B but God you know
protected life with my ears no brother
so we as practitioners little brats yes
when I feel fabulous
she said Betsy Koon Wow think it's a
fact
Wow medulla Chelsea factory everything
is maintaining the reverse switch
precision inner tube when SS Osuna I
don't know for the benefit of others
like how do we do give you right the
third gear National Service and you told
the register so snow angel
not block the girl get Yugi no it's not
luggage if planting seeds in the wrong
way
think about it so there's no being the
stochastic national median the idea I
think with wonder makers I mean now
we're talking nuclear power here we're
talking money groups I mean your son I
see what second for the dinosaur suit if
you begin to control that factor a
second term you get far completely
videos to listen to that it's at me like
this big wheel truck or the sole but
surely do not see this is your boy I'm
gonna let them but it's these thousands
of other education morning there little
tiny seeds
it's a morning kiss you know begin to
manifest in unpleasant forums
considering putting less of me up really
I don't know I
we had a Pilates class today unless for
me it was like destroy he was my little
are these things
I wonder what like I just got like an
aluminum oil mustard seeds ripen it was
good at the preserves love teaching
you know toughest classes in which and
people thought I had to show the cluster
dozen stuff bloopers but that was just
the opening points I felt like that
happen but of course the second or yeah
I can bank on that you know us
understand maybe
but on my towers to you mr. Palacios up
so we Cydonia w practical and less
humidity with magic Adam excuse us we as
a career that's I said the show there's
this idea mr. Vinh dear don't you you'll
never get her meet a result if actually
never society publications yet much not
casually dining depositional I think of
the hospitals reason the links that how
many disappointments have we had in the
last quarter of on your gospel is a
busted knee would why no portion why do
we put your morning more expectations
that we say mother died nickel but I'm a
pretty cool organist on you my bottom
layer to the second episode you see
regret yes a Roberto as simplified as
the first steps are it's the most
elegant got me a blue percentage like
Amanda watching Theory Christian have
formally look at which my did she get
you were there it's messy tunis enough
ensign Urian up Rasta anymore airline
Robert so we can't be disappointed when
we don't get what we were the more his
almost would be and it doesn't happen we
shouldn't get disappointed choice
episode to the same and so this is this
is what comes about if you didn't do the
Karma you watch the British gorgeousness
that the nepotism okay and yesterday two
sisters there's a debate in my mind
about that because of some unused
Abdullah example right now don't want to
do she said that she was at the same
time so there McConnell to dishonor that
area here we are kind
we're creating cars right now listen I'm
Karla Brown is chess it's happening
right now
that's what I thought but I was just
that is we're taught to more commas
what should kind of mine right after
there's only a tiny moment of change
when when another karma is created - be
fine right what's the dope God will kill
them - in our actions we create karma
school age which was the most powerful I
could use someone emotions
yeah are thinking it gets us in the most
kindest daughter honestly when you
retreat was one of these Roylott amazing
eye openers about television about
patterns of thoughts got my mind
I mean else's ninety percent or so
they're hardwired into our daily dose
because the pressure on the
consciousness that they were puts us
money in the swarm of going for my
sister's friend they were just behind
why do you suck us I'd be do I I
wouldn't be in deep subtle mindfulness
I'd be washing the dishes in Hoboken
suffering sort of Tibet and it started
when I was seven that was good
that happened upon sort of the
preservation less obscure I to take you
with me Monica goes up region is up what
I'm saying it's a source as much because
it all happen just like that evolution
is crash pattern - master - Turkestan
you mean is unsound each distillation
those were more important moments in a
deep subtle other places that digital
board you donkey my mantle but she'll be
there it up and you do more
you see it's researching in a world of
ordinary things which new media possibly
having our thought process is not
something we just do a little bit on the
blue death but they just don't click or
immediate that's it always at the
dealing with our medium actually mass or
some number times the diet change me
process and we can interpret even with
the third law of karma internalizing
aspects agree need to resolution episode
Nakata and we've also done my share
Domino garage
you know why didn't I get permission to
be on your bullets will push on your
bust a little spin
why can't I afford you know a two-week
vacation when my worship was ordered
orphanage in white yeah but you know I
don't know
all the above what Shibuya you know just
it's like they're literally Palomita
younger than us to lubricate the
a style of apology just a minute boots
and there's something that we call
oxygen money yesterday on kiss love
Namibian government system in DC I
perceive a justice to us as many
aperture the background that you can
send the planet and when spiking his
linguistic comfort me and you do much
about you know so I mean if you're P
notions
pre-crushed okay you have sit down the
brain here we don't we can't afford it
you know but she's right like just
double and then just let it go and
rejoice that you had enough cash to give
to Diamond Mountain I coulda in your
wallet when you motorist if you want to
0 velocity ponder to study the you
establish your stuff there Academy
commuters abortion evaporating and I
should spank the procrastination so car
nice car get the dealer so next slide
share J but you miss our good news you
cannot avoid them just reduce our ocean
Amish
that's the many more verses visit
corrosive personal history Hawaii
thorough so Jays not so good news
because you can't avoid the results of
your paranoia
continue mortars presenters don't sleep
I see these two thugs you know we'd like
to accentuate the positive I'm risk just
a company I was into the eyes and tides
little glasses my right in the karmic
course we talk about your seeds or stain
questioning look good as there's no
suspect is a bicycle mobility processor
just a with the princess sees a source
of that economist Chris a minion it has
me grasp we know we want to spin your
mom effective look at him I don't know
yeah we can do all the you know there's
something called your story spheres of
unitary sphere a Diana the giver is
empty and the action of the you suppose
do some fuzzy I found me in the hospital
Diana to procrastinate in the back of
your mind at least eight compartment
with the line yeah yeah which is
isn't touched and it's stained
so at the bar choice we say you're at
the mercy McGorry my own perfect
seasonal watching Moloch domination I
Alicia that the idea of the essence of
emptiness of everything that we do it
has to be exponentially very fine the
actual practice of seed planting
[Music]
rejoicing in my process if you start to
the pros to hire radishes Frances Jim
lutes
what a motion with the same integrity
passages yeah it's it's it's a process
that the brothers Couture and where's
your chance
what about the objects that we know so
it's a beautiful movie better generate
ceaseless attention and ask granted or
in a ferocious attack
say it again does it show us no yeah
give me an example of a US diplomat of a
so Columbia economy just gonna say it
again
shadows okay a teacher the bridge energy
tells you yeah what else I stations for
certain I up yet the circular vehicle
Diane you see parents who said Mary
Reggie Dylan just cuz all the DJ yeah
yes Reggie today what about a CI or I
got a CI no Muslim girls a PSAP it's a
key Russia especially now suddenly it's
funny we you know we don't in our in our
system this is just a high comic objects
Masuka can ask it objective we people do
their due diligence when they give money
investment is a chance of British
intelligence shake some partisan
legislation that would use for a hundred
years but suddenly
Terry andouille the sugar fascinating it
says because the merit of that for your
mother's dollar you see opinion washing
but I guarantee that the wisdom of
whatever that's gonna jungwirth into the
world it's a language that you
understand you can't assert apologize
motorist you'll get the wisdom from that
page that you put up together it does
apply to you a dollar I think it's a
dollar twenty nine lots of do stores of
those threats or I would start to
wouldn't Solomon child Osama gun side
and that's not including inflation of
the Indian rupee their catch and
fluttering seventy right now Anderson
says relative but them
okay everybody gets raises several
chairs less pollution but you see the
investment you make with a conscious
contribution is just go to the butchers
a source known as see wasn't to your
teacher is a nice vegetable cars Susanna
Cordova so Katie says it have to be
about saving text because I found
surprising TX the founders Without
Borders they do I wasn't the cheapest
granny is any component and you
progressed the revolution has a high
convert companionship to your action to
get specialist we made for service
company entre karmic objects we have to
think about okay it's very interesting
chemically is story learns to pay taxes
usually applied you know Louis's famous
novel again it's apparent to people that
know how to create loopholes it's too
hard a lot of ridiculous
I have kirk dillard gear you know your
boy did no law against that has to do
also with the correlation of honesty at
the governmental machinery let's each
isness my cell is responsible for
for you we have the lewiston's D in your
system wherever minimize distance I
could just pick those two began to just
really distant system karma compromises
that you to cool the British writer
blood with our stupid sister that we
share in yours which I said he was
mumbling correlations another is rosetta
Khalil and say Kaddish companion tip
don't keep in stock I woke up Madhu my
doing the actions of these four amazing
steps so district would you look shocked
oh no a to do its adult sure it's funny
there are certain time since above with
carly's chemistry me and telling us to
do why do you have to address Gazzola
all of these seats ripened in her life
she eats right position they her life is
transfer give you the system that's
really if the chorus would must just she
just the shank I was above yourself
super job of our dreams wonderful meal
about amidst a beautiful car mixed
acuity Christina so has to do with the
point of the taxi animated machinist
because there's a smear chair in the
process of death Mr Francis is smerte
what happens to your seats stop requests
am assuming lava
what actually is going on stop this with
what's happening inside karmically stop
Elizabeth economy just play the industry
everything is running out
Sousa gunch's seeds are popping like
crazy
Simula yours grows our supporters to
being destroyed between get roses senses
are closed to see such an easy situation
our solution is a conscious and so
there's this comes into the whole point
of what seed will take you what karma is
gonna take you guys no risk okay car
went a bit busy for it says Chivo your
next rebirth
and this is where we have to really work
it the volumes are the portions
nobody's rung it up with a lesser
economy just give me Simeon Lana yeah
Geshe Michaels teacher used to watch the
new Wednesday night just insulted them
and there used to be a beautiful girl on
a short maybe Zoo on them to do on that
example professed ideals you know it's
mine solar systems where the piratical
open sewers I bet you me doing actually
expose later but he did that to us was
that like a quince that you don't see
that going to the freezer finalizing
sort of the bustling is here it was cake
what that the year so you're going to
see a nice little but yours good that
you're banished are you going to be
fully engaged
with the controlling of that it would
just look they got going to control it
that may be some way it had to do a lot
so do you think it's the uncertainty
karma was tempered in oneness Jess
pretty well especially good slides tell
you unless you sparse leather service
because I John with this no West Jeff so
the good news is there's only three
questions to your homework ocean oysters
Russia's Damascus leave a person you see
yes everything is a person or shown
you're not George my Anika Copeland well
that's depressing
you girl cheer on your Tunisia so on
brother you should say no because Nia
doesn't let you get a shock come up with
designs for booger sugar granules in yet
I know exactly hundred avid games like
toys in the country if it isn't more
glitches John we have eighteen courses
you know storm would be to three-year we
could kill it feature this life in
beyond night I like that for the
meantime no pakka
do you agree that life has an issue and
a journo a post a honest truth I'm not
sure Drazen was which votes and final
cut but I just read it was daughter
much and their meditations just said the
Polish crews after formation to say if a
million euros less was my last word you
know it's just so poor person I don't
like that type from integer estoy why
don't we get yes some space so it's
certain semitic open your stuff put in
the door mr. nothing why don't we ask
you sit on the truth when you said you
audience meditation I don't mean to talk
so sweetly what's good I stopped doing
dishes sort of pets ordinary itch is my
last breath which is more busted it's so
hard to get
put the gas pretty much efficiency but
no much possibility that the dailies
teach and you can subdue No
yeah sure should do more healthy young I
have Medicare and good any diamond it's
the whole group over at sure that you
bite you know possible future you know I
have another ten years I know him
initially dishes that there's my
holidays still present
yeah he's not in with us witnesses of a
premarital assurance that the party was
Morgan distresses after personal
training and practice with practical at
subliminally so we're at the fortune is
over - it's the mind space demo stud
it's almost like Leviticus for more fear
or you're too strong you know
beginningless question toys with me
because instinctive solution I'd it's
just and something up in your mind
provides total firm butter kisses
landing at the pre-crash now so in your
toolkit you should have a really
questionable instrumental doesn't of it
Oh Chicago say assessment data a
particle
is that good that moon with her own
little awful but it's what they took who
as was introduced a chest there's
something in our system called the
fourth flower and it's too early to talk
yet that is route that the NASA Academy
description the last one is that we are
literally she was their design of our
future which is implied by the pollution
at the onion on let me cut it suppose to
mean you go anymore in cannot say and
it's kind of beautiful
no we're the precursor to Swift or
screeches with nobody here in this room
so they procrastinate she says within
qualms with authority for this ruthenium
nutrients motivation manual so that
whatever was going through was an
enormous change um that I was responding
arrived at system one of us meets
publish never met by such this email is
she'll eat your mind
most of about the Buddha she reason it
can we design more than was daily
designed year well we first want to get
away mismatch Alan you people first one
its partners in working with this reason
you and if you're Jerry more aesthetic
quality ministers to be presentable DOMA
you have a theater I just you know I
thought I took the kool-aid and I bought
the package this my students over to get
out where Watson is Calissa
few maybe future Reapers before you're
completely done emotion which images
shop are going to sponsor us exactly
thing Whistler the habituation about -
behind edge to the previous Commission
in sequence
third one was that this vehicle was a
programmer on the median age list of a
small car to start with the street
corner Eunice is a designer so sterno
Patoka says not a mess in this room just
a nick tour is not what the killings
have this possibility yet so I can take
a little nibble of my dish just one
here's a drug training in the teachings
of Atlas Gonzalez 11 emotional
everything here
so what I did is media wanna do is just
see me on you've got about the reader I
want you to kind of think about yeah I
drove over Township abortion Purdue male
there's always in my world a hesitation
meatiest was telling okay
summoning usual on you but if it's just
displaying ago that there's this other
suggest backwater my secret towards says
man you mean enough says let us go out
so she's a bit of up gauntlet you know
what a gauntlet is like it's always
there's some karma that will ripen
unexpected to say this to the furthest
took that quicker there's enough for you
yes an area to say never get anybody yet
like I don't know whatever whatever that
she said the rest of prophetic Ottomans
brother late you've sick that are even
after there's a poster all of I what
I've done here to see what room is still
appropriate region that happened again
yet the process what I could have sort
this is someone wrote you know the
discomfort of Margo finance to you just
comfort to those two yeah but do you
think that gestures are just where there
are seeds that right now are you sure
got a little storage that was good
evening
first watching Nia come for another
aspect of myself for not just doctors
sitting perception of seats retaliation
was Macalester torture me motion and I
mean yeah it's my emotions good better
and different I will allow extraordinary
or just or maybe a sec need a little
wood natural put it because ships and
we're here together we're just finished
in which social progress my machine yeah
yeah when you can point it to me I don't
think to dismiss for this place at the
mystery she took 15 years to purify and
the mist knows look the glass is little
but she's something that she says weeds
just got me skip lefse from us can
change your mind more is a minute or so
says - so take advantage of that miss
portage it'll shunts I'm just sayin
karmically I gotta meet you please let
me come find you into me watch if she
knows but we took lose yourself words or
through it but investors especially in
her the Disney more that we talked about
earlier this there's just be quickened
does adjustable wrenches difference
which is coordinates this trip was three
presents dead in order to escape the
circle of life most of us would say
white actions to do this we must use to
that's a formal way of saying
at least he has mexicana first list the
far - post-gazette pretty good cheetah
is a qualifier there's another aspect
that's the downside is the best picked
Authority what happens overseas under
certain external in the realms of
existence there are no rocks restore and
yes Jimmy Snuka must be a perceptual
Sophie Buddhism or talk about where
little doll realms the creamiest other
true gear The Hungry Ghost round is
divorced move the tension which leverage
double bogey bogey and it's not some
self-existent play this is a quick
little the girls room is you know 180
nice to go but it's delicious
as I put the thoughts of doing this was
no historian while every social Duda but
in the sense of this idea of Columbus
mr. Homma
the car what a sense of what would it
take for us to realize that renunciation
is a faculty shortness what three words
two buses are not storage in here to
fund a mimosa budgets at the talk ELISA
it might be a good idea to do a little
bit of low power low around don't meet
your thoughts on the nation just go I
will open your blog well yeah because I
sunglass moment so much just we just
walk to repair much as done went through
she spewed Estrada
yeah ranches Massa Jackson Bikram yoga
you saw rapid repetition sorry with but
and
and I used to do a tongueless mysterious
material Rihanna privileges of
procrastinate source wait Acharya chief
ah da ya da de ganancia the dust was
more say to mr. Shekhar Adafruit Estrada
attica schedule only an hour ago Boca
Juniors but is novice potato in a
wishlist routed to extend a group an
extended to cover system job mr. Smith
versus karma can bring us to these much
Jewish district most Muslims and
emotions each button with the toaster
because my fish was just was just with
us and some women and various
resistances and robbery investigation
they see the practical efficiency and
mostly alone but you so discuss item
stuff but and append like yes Wichita's
so in the weirdest will go for the ring
that was also the donation for beings to
achieve what else is throughout the
Angela's mysterious character mean you -
you miss one let's go through some of
these logistics aspects right dosage is
eg shake was this perspective yet to the
retirees would have suffered a moment
won't be so delicate reported some
tostring me never satisfied
you got a note of the tourists so Mick
Jagger had it right the Jagger Vilnius
gazelle I can't get no satisfaction it's
pretty self-explanatory
you guys said that I want to buy a
plasma dish we always want something
else right wishing that let him chew out
the board shot
say it again yeah only the good things
tokoha wrong yeah that's true at the
viola when's the last time you were
unsatisfied the level of possibly did
ask the ruling Neil do let's put in
there that dinner that was alone I don't
know like I took the wrong pasta is that
yoga what the neutral post it you know
there is the gluten-free or soy beverage
so there was a non-gluten of pasta
cheese macaroni and I didn't know those
you know it's like anticipating I love
still or you're certainly the bestest
sit on gluten
you know and I and then you chew it till
it's a little things like that the
madding Kitakyushu shinky the king you
what understa
but the bigger things are the board
service in relationship to our
materialistic reality cassettes is less
than with tendencies could analyst you
know there's a statistic
Easter is 37 percent of luxury goods in
the world 30 of every Gucci or Louis
Vuitton bag it's a lot of surplus or
more to those of Keith I so much you
know and believe it door a friend of
ours had a bag and she said when I
should but the review blossoms thousand
dollars of a sorcerer and a lot center
face shaken over it like it's a piece of
forever
a little morning I guess maybe go
[Music]
associating that I find in China that
they've reached a certain destruction
during wealth and materialism
it's so cool because that's the
beginning of what this solid sure or is
a search for something different that's
not gonna push through a little more
true than it is at you because you can
only put so many of those in your closet
that goes to vesicular much positive
stuff the preservative best thing you
could go to the black market and buy the
fake me that unfortunate remark of the
great but dimly little people so the
difference so not sure what the times
but yeah I think the one solution we are
unsatisfied to some degree when yodeler
settles the person is different because
I don't know that's a right my solution
is reason or wasn't met these men is
still there she's like yeah this is a
depressing those short than usual the
lowest so we yeah we die over and over
my own that I am Russ let's me cross the
veil we forget that speed as you can
with the granite so were sublime should
all just no add sure I thought would
change gotta remove would suggest bruh
what do each it is me right
it's not some postulate often we
navigate back because the wounds on
others get better without I think
worried you know sleeved ocean pretty
good wine it though we got to this place
got without good with us because Naz
that's just so depressing it though
which shouldn't even show that nor do we
want to do doesn't effective canisters
items the quenches at this is just no
more than
it's interesting is that we have such
beginningless time experiences we've
died and shoved out a lot is the size of
she's mountains high owns it a little uh
birth and rebirth good so every wooden
skis Sakurajima probable or sensor
system of seekers patella tibia or
storage Ilic well we certainly can learn
and experiments which it's their only
glove them put down looking at the club
which you might Jim Lee everybody would
achieve with the ship ships as a sub boy
get out and bring it on you aware of it
and come back with the ship's yes boy or
maybe very nice utility shorts it is a
fortress know what a good tube is when
you wanna do but sit toko downrange on
still the developers some people do I
mean I mean I know people who have very
clear lucky just like you didn't get
better which isn't short covering that
she's swimming that later i I don't I I
think you could develop delicious
reachable practical you see three makes
three regions very porous reasoning like
is we just rotating the treatment at the
top button you take you towards
encourage add those two roast come with
disco hot but I think reason is a
protection device because do we actually
experience because the the pro
system of retiring crew gear other sort
of bullet I'm just not censorship as
long as 100 make economist Kazushige
nojima God was nice to meet you
direction
hacked away firstly I must get on that
stump what would be typical so she looks
miss prism there's a real interesting in
in past lives in our time mr. leaking
disperses what community is a bus no yes
I'm manoeuvres are you take a trip
attacks and I teach at do you think I
don't know anything about it last week
about the Caliph etcetera stupid City
rebel demolish the notion was for the
image in revolutions coupling dyskinesia
scrappy near Karbala louis zoo - ipoh
Nevada - in Westchester describes a
sonic described at every image was
monster said are devote a
manipulative of the Rosen Shastras dish
how many lifetimes squid countries news
monitor stones from wastewater pond in
the stories of the boot order boot you
know there's so many stories thought
today was bit surprising just uber and
that's something that's a good credit
sister nor its experience and receive a
bursary lotion in my car workers
we gotta stop a cheese teacher to Carmen
its margin is the Krueger garage
disposable in here we should visit
automotive design so food is sure
communicative we did much much at the
ball over there as the bully who spoke
Irish English
why do we have to take our extension of
aperture amigos
but I just read surah bakra sister Danny
we were drugged you Eclair sir mr.
macadam Express cheap but sure what's
the correlation Chum could it lets it
than us why we why do we want which
understood when you rule this I mean I
was the children of a desk with sabor
safest under live Shiva thought mr.
popular there are only two kinds of
peace according to see what what
cheapest rucious - the master philosophy
re Giga thought it was reversal of this
re Egypt oh and yet if there's no other
there's neutral New York we're hot mr.
hodda there only there there are only
two kinds of beings just oak Eduardo
sushi is known as a plane yet according
to us know the master's program Western
I was running with it I had a shoe
blizzard so quiet stood and I'm go at it
we're in training you know what will
change the time we were seeing
accompanies us at in love with the
sheets subway forgive me then the
positiv accustomed each element of a
blog when you give my doesn't give me a
total good said the writer give me those
words my best use them so committee rods
for coming down
dice numbers more than lists there's no
sleep which i bought the purse will
change you support your a
discreet deep and you might study more
with words but I does anyone don't exist
you know your past life it's not a
process reason because this produces two
she just quit open a dojo yeah corner is
it a good one Hiroshi yeah crying
so is a hard life but there's a little
blood okay that's cool okay for
iguana we must take perfect attacks
leadership with other audiences Nova is
Noah its ability presumably whistling
yeah I mean think of the pain of it but
then we tell the Borla it's all good
water swim mama it's like they're born I
don't have memories and then you think a
cosplayer Lanyon but there's no
memories are in there get the time we
just released a prostitute to do it as
Rosen his agency llamas it's a text was
no hazard school commands SCADA that was
me but replenished again and we know a
lot of bees that are the negative energy
is not going for some miracle a miracle
most of the three resulting and you're
fast forward over the next few years
it's guaranteed you you're not thinking
about next Friday's when the Duma most
eligible bachelor movie audiences what
persecution and not some parts of the
world well I'm not giving me stuff Mira
[Music]
you know we have the sustainability of
also what unless used astray but just
posting those words so I wouldn't ever
do manual Dutch it's it's part of who
you are
you had the chest I walked over years
where does this really switch
we should achieve at the corner he was
his dust room procrastinate illusion
Oscar on television message for the a
mister Bimini tea roses and CEO gray the
children are some dinner
the America at the new Retina it should
you made the soup Virginia at the now
which at the knob which no more but I
gotta cut up which no I'm not a only
lets extra ordinarily amazing novotná
persons over yet no yeah we have to
learn it again anything right well now
with mothers or changes on the horizon
yeah a little does she changing
constantly changing status fortune is
really she stops not sure that you know
Cigna might say of the sky services
arises during any camera Breslin
reassurance from her schedule yes you
witness to get on me course I don't mean
Oscars business course he thought issue
yeah well sitting in New York there's
only your can I had worked for a company
for 21 years
yeah what goes when compiling it careers
lots attention good bloke ready yet of
saying you know it was a good company I
had Orozco and she plan or a bullet
I was through my birthday you know
I just reminding you
I thought mortgage in you look it gives
my clothes because of gelatinization PS
cause I'm wish yeah well sorry was to
Soraka Davichi overall soon the company
said oh you know you have all this money
he come finest girls as you know us will
show that you just may get business why
could that be the dream
I think is a pratical that in history
which is worse to be emotional fine
which was the robot of can also do a
Merrill Lynch arena yet oh my no I was
now in the process of doing renewables
processes just inserted three doctorates
Cheney and a retreat close my house in
New York is a girl's word on New York
you buy a home shall be procrastinate
promoter exist in unity three to double
my parents died a shady tree then also
down boy Thunder cap which the garage
which the approaches foster square which
Morris range it's an issue and a
thousand by Jenna question she was like
this it should amount of money Adam
blogger ominous imagining and it was
this bubble that burst in the tech
companies good I'm good I'm little
subtle index Cox
yeah with the same Roxana shifter
typical IQ skiff mighty Allah protect us
one that was alive yeah he episode
they don't let their doom attack that I
bought dawn where I was not even stir
this what she wished me yet doesn't
Ebola serving the restaurant karma
really took the yeah now you're not
feelin so another key notes only hairs
down on stock level is done money and he
called on the peroneal he was on Bo Bo
Bo zone
you have lost its logic yeah potatoes
just was bitter rain yeah and he
apologized I said look you owe Nazarene
Ilse all opposed - wrong yes because
almost finishing Brazilian a blood
sausage I've seen other people not agree
shows the visit this is like utilities
sure finish on the plazas tomorrow
yes the prettiest consulting was cos øz
nice to achieve garzooka people know as
constituted factors absolutely yes -
Chris Jones a conscience no brother
chooses to be abortion is tyranny Bruno
until this doesn't dig legend was when
he asked one else to me another he's got
that I'm what that six months
later he says mrs. Christian Apple
Church a question my friend Jim just a
little here's your first installment no
Drogo J humble my business solution now
gentlemen at the lead pad know what - a
mediator way whatever solution you
Buddha to the kisser it humanely $20
ongoing solution yes it's just about the
game do tablets at Austria had
resiliency even path leads are
distressed missions
problems nature right logic are no down
it was very good but there it is right
like wow I you know I had a lose
everything
boom you have Schubert Adele boomer said
to learn always such an bleep every
seven or eight years Ian I didn't get
all seven worship yet New York
it is not session life in a constant
change of money what is me is referred
to us
no Stan the same or same union that's
got nice rainy yes there's my guy people
say yeah Mouse at the orchard on when it
comes to town so visually it's always
changing the stay analyst Manisha
Fortuna its leadership yeah
so John Lennon wrote a song down on the
basalt beach near hot instinct are my
son with my demise is my ad master
accattone
he can't take nothing with you but
you're seen your mother's mature
zetsubou closer right you must lose
everything and you can only take your
suitcase full of carbon stupid air
shuttle where's mr. Iijima dance we can
meet you scream now you know people that
are in you know under a hospice care
literally lose except to reroute and we
go to Roberto frigid woods and stumble
yeah yeah 8020 capital engines are still
bad parity
sorry for annuity paragraph simple must
because oh not was doing right on
Christian strategy on Christians version
roses one more dress a reality check yet
managed to see what vehicle Shimon
approach tutorial apps too scared to
achieve a poster design error message
and request a yeah is this kind of
situation to attack I was it was and
nothing else Anthony shoe worst at the
motors at Subway except your beautiful
seats
so it was pretty crash like she man and
that's what we're here for you whatever
the bathroom is this one this is a
projecting karma that's the ultimate
importantly what are the tablets Alicia
karma columnar Carmona shaky economy
tiara
whatever we suggest yeah it is Jewish
duh do it now what this judge such as a
luscious little she responds which you
order so much before you have to do it
now which much go get the dog excited
just by me the present version Buddhism
we figured it out Moses accordingly
should to support it
and you can try it thank you for superb
roaming it gets my closer this Moses
Jill the presenter is interpretive
community touch this Mirta yeah that's
the last one yeah bus lignin so
renunciation I'm talking about attrition
yeah yeah stop it sprouts in a person's
heart once he has medical a storm cellar
pregnant immunity rule Astrid an Aries
choose to go cottage any attack that
they choose to perform a machine that
recipe was it natural English
mathematician when you've meditated yes
so that the p90
moments wish for the good things it
doesn't matter no one Ukrainian
corrosion you say with its international
to mean gang in North Apple changes for
Buddhist people achieve at Marion
depression
that you've been the shoulder the attend
yes the chest was like that's what door
le marché rim oh it's here there's this
sort of set and yeah you know I
don't know giving everything away at any
brothers to fish a lot of does that
renunciation is Tito Jenny at the system
are sustainably deep Stan you good book
or speaking I beside this truck said
process as for bursting and renunciation
is really shake my eyes that brings you
tell us some whatever additional that I
provided direct almost as well really
consistent the fully engaged aspect of
even unless it's an open our hearts
solution was get no better described as
a shelter that was more scattered on us
yesterday just blah delicious better
delicious Chase Utley
what burrows yes Lois what across
[Music]
Oakland is to approach chassis college
but she will show gorilla movie - ah so
neutral where is a bedroom
tambul watch corrosive approach such
like Tetris da Lorenson is dead but
Nizam wishes the cassettes an Aquarius
to my registry is viscous Nicholas food
positions as Danny yeast animal predator
which chronicles avatar of to promulgate
dragons which is plan
Varro's push a new tack resna to be yeah
good procedures so Palmerston name is
the taboo DiCaprio Priscilla
supermarkets understand if approached
ball and strategic Nika stop on my
bloopers testicle procedures numbers not
a meteor Watsa nurse Angela to approach
the student assured she's just one whose
Apple child Roger cook soup Amish
catalyst number would rise and seriously
yeah I mean you don't matter like you
know it was in check positions to
vertical several Reverend alluded should
deal there's a it prescription mrs.
Daniel yet wasn't ipanema has to to
Nationals relative good do catalyst so a
certain assertions summer semesters name
Buddha
Easter dusters Nadia Petryk nakulan as
the champion of the Taurus that over any
polish you are reality this parent that
was said you so much does not see Peters
needs to go directly to use for media
its mother it was mothering I mean it
was want us to Eastern it's like you
must do their business I'm not seeing my
world the way ideally want us yet we
need to sway me and thinking forget what
I tell ya certainly premier the whole
story about Minnie Tracy monaster with
me is Michael gorgeous look bust leading
a blunt yet though so nice nice dudes
don't meet you putz they use shifts
gorgeous little metaphor Nicholson and
if actually very strong message his
publicity she always managed to but this
village for you to help their business
not like it's Jost attempt on waters
they know what you're you know if you're
beginningless and they've know your past
and your possessions and Lajoie accounts
uh is not a militia partly it's hard to
jump listen you know that there's a lot
about you
we must Bezemer
become the fullest evolutionary
possibility of this eyeball never even
looks on
to do other than that she's worse than
she was to issue a thing yet potential
for you but themselves it's
exponentially impossible to even have
our minds Gator get around it explain in
silence to energy countless bodies this
is not your mother's Canyon until Isis
completely things wrong people that are
helping us get out to the most
predictable my god no literal it's any
question anymore Nick words with chest
roads so and maybe - uh you're
suspicious enough to think that was
noble isn't me to give some kind of an
answer for everybody to hear her or
something one of the things that I said
earlier though is that you know super
system our enemies it's the curse of our
dilemma it's a brick led to the things
is it's the thing we must remove and
that passion is so it's not simply that
is my charge my taste when it doesn't
become normal
shame that you know you know
understand led to it somewhere and
there's really nothing that I have to do
it was not a slab is intrusive no Jorge
Ramos nice yeah see the Express no it
was more less to pause to listener issue
a solution or sustain the secret of
illusion lat
I mean usually with Chile it was not
ideal
we must say more a business because it
still a which those love beats hard
about normally does not be see the extra
gesture every day what can happen
Thomas presentation who can I meet what
practice should I do
Chemical Street Kaku practice till it
became ago to Remini mindfulness ye
yummy pasta unlimited resource analyst
magalie initiative miracle predict about
palmistry Gilman Avenue so many the
Misha
suitably chosen Imams Bathsheba firstly
we have minutes I sure wish I may not
yes
hey Shiva Minister approach Kassadin
promote was created bodhichitta me a
person locus machine is put industry yet
vulture to yarmulke polish each group
but he cheated on cacao is posted on
Oprah more marketable pristine cockatoo
curry Lyrids premium was Preetam posted
a free was created
it's a correlation with the direct
perception of a bean
history else's woman's brilliant study
honest responses firstly vegetative
proud re and you have somewhere else
Rose rightness and Aleppo chest open
rate it is this beautiful contrast is
what is to watch is Rita is Jabez
quality this was a good book a good book
it certainly crash television it's the
other side of the coin the broadness to
[Music]
study after a chest chest where
experience at Oprah more specific
absolutely definitely taste
receptor antagonist of real meetings us
a few knows that you can take bank on to
finish their circular oceans but it's
not when you have that experience
without developer Lancet some dog
doesn't go away was a bush like then
your retina so it's a real winner States
and I've shooter starters so there's so
many different explanations of
bodhichitta mr. Logan I guess I was
possessed of massive Bretting
practitioners and having the wish to
gain bodhichitta and do them in my
military budget to Flushing
means does be feeling a subtle
difference of how you express your
sister don't garage
Carter would be a mere an expression of
oh my gosh I was alerted by both persons
got doing in my was worthless
you know that that reduce whereas the
Buddhist would
the police personally better give mr.
Lansing give and that's that's part of
some sort of me if in charge devolution
are practical and it you know you get
those taste in through your retrieve
those custom pool chairs of the roughly
it needed three they say it's like that
that it cracks open
the iron vies cracks Hilton
did you work it starts to pour out of
you just an avisaurus cravat see at
least ability currently at the monocle
is adjustable in every teacher he
assisted the booze netiquette moving
Zack see if you can do talk very much is
Joseph the shortest shortest shortest
one more shot in Weber's to Marlene was
big
a storage locker video posted on the
promoter of your video so you move the
violet repeaters Dania the towers to
Istanbul a stored procedure to us
l'addition reasoning Moodle they are yes
they it's pretty removers manager the SS
with me yes mr. Rd was it no in the
early stages of their life Geshe Michael
is very clear about that he said it's
like solution-driven
presenting the good in got nancy boy i
was the llama and he's rebuilding his
royalty in there when you wish -
establish a so he gets spoiled but it
was you know it's like questionable like
is he really the reincarnation of
so-and-so and but Gish michael has said
that Geshe Michael said earlier around
the age of foolishness is the amount of
seed start opening a saloon stroke I
just wish your mouth yeah I mean and
that they're actually innocent she
became such a great debater
it was fast all sitios know the
leakiness my ripening happened at the
age of birth daughter of 16 and then it
it just took off he was just showing
shoulders to that clarity that you know
the the direct perception of emptiness
doctor here to possibly see them you
actually experience that today I knew he
just got that the politicians testing is
perfectly noise noise noise or to data
thank you then thank you very well sure
oh one more you notice my grass cloth
not reaching I mean I used to pretty
lonely ouput not the yellow my
passes - Nikita - Mira
he loves leadership yep a - total genius
no brainer she will provide irrigation
Michael each other stone employer from
Pakistan to quit a crushed mrs. manleigh
no crying I was - whispering Russia
pristine amok yep yet new McGraw I just
read about it and I still publish nabla
Virginia grocery store religion that's
something that we're all dealing with at
Austin my question is progressive
society it's it's meditation it really
is like you start with you know yet
there's no scholar gonna start with one
human being
so now what should I be accepting
there's no that one human being who is
in emotional pain or physical pain or
mental there's never no other signal
yeah and you once online board
/ - I should share the motion particle
backwards in teen mr. Childers
established it as a mirror system or
diminish - you ate at all not that you
be not afraid for small much Daniels
right gray roots isn't ordinary open to
the Fatima she was just appreciate the
blood crater more than just one so
that's just a single example right we
underestimate the power of them that's
it
why is his secret moistures a practicum
on no cousin look a little the boy
secretly bright okay
did you bid on our what good I just wish
it was he used the Sheila Pinette posted
removers happen was similar gas
arranging to see the Googlebot affected
by motion repeaters National Buddha
Prussia Gordon let's go see our you know
you know you know it's nice Rose was
thinking that you can see those losers
Oh losers question trace this is Julia
cup golden about Shore as Jesus is
Porter practical tourism a Cessna
Citation so I do little things for
people who you understand may have some
problems but unless it's my linkages to
muscle giggles love for much the
rejoicing of the tiny seats we do all
day long we don't a creditor Wellman is
the customer doesn't has brothers
exactly Samantha forever finding
additional traverses omnipresent never
directed to the years older Jeffrey
child released his most ability and
immobile zucchini register together the
bourgeois she said sir nobody cheat
thank you so much
I see well sure I see what ratio
[Applause]